<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>術</title>
    <link>https://byronz.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 術</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 | 朱曉清 | &lt;small&gt;powered by&lt;/small&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;gohugo.io&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 13:17:01 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://byronz.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum Snippet</title>
      <link>https://byronz.github.io/posts/scrum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 13:17:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byronz.github.io/posts/scrum/</guid>
      <description> Tip for new JIRA UI, you can type username to do quick filter
 user name by alphabeta order
- abirrell - acaron - bzhu - cengsstrom 🐞 - dsoloviev - gkankava - hhussein - izenbaei - jlee - jlau - lesposo - larabuli - mrivet - pteng - shshah - twang 🐞 - vho  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JWT</title>
      <link>https://byronz.github.io/posts/jwt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 10:53:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byronz.github.io/posts/jwt/</guid>
      <description>Structure  JJJJ.PPPPPPP.SSSSSSSS
  JOSE Payload Signature  RFCs  JWS JWT  Usage Validation Algorithm  7.2. Validating a JWT
When validating a JWT, the following steps are performed. The order of the steps is not significant in cases where there are no dependencies between the inputs and outputs of the steps. If any of the listed steps fail, then the JWT MUST be rejected &amp;ndash; that is, treated by the application as an invalid input.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Narcos</title>
      <link>https://byronz.github.io/posts/eng-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 17:15:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byronz.github.io/posts/eng-1/</guid>
      <description>I just watched 3 seasons of netflix&amp;rsquo;s series Narcos, really enjoyed the south american landscape scene and latino guitar. The script is about 70% Español and 30% English.
kingpin - キングピン S3E1 The Kingpin Strategy
 a person or thing that is essential to the success of an organization or operation.
 smuggler synonyms: - trafficker - mule  paranoid  characterized by suspiciousness, persecutory trends, or megalomania behaving in a paranoid manner with accusations of persecutions</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Binoculars, Refractor or Reflector?</title>
      <link>https://byronz.github.io/posts/telescope/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 13:47:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byronz.github.io/posts/telescope/</guid>
      <description>I was interested to buy my first telescope, and here are my criteria:
 portable - I need to transport it to dark site and don&amp;rsquo;t want to spend 1 hour setup everything in the cold dark planertry vs deep dark - this is hard to tell, see moon or saturn will be excited for the first time, but what about the next budget - 200$ - 500$  Optical theory Binoculars Refractor Reflector Designed by Issac Newton in 18xx to solve one common problem in refractor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My blog site setup tips</title>
      <link>https://byronz.github.io/posts/notes_hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 16:10:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byronz.github.io/posts/notes_hugo/</guid>
      <description>The first mistake you might have about Github Pages is about the subtle difference between User &amp;amp; Org Pages and Project Page. It takes me a while to realize that the first page can only point to the static content in master branch, which you don&amp;rsquo;t have the possiblity of switching to gh-page branch or master/doc (you can do that with project repo though). So you only publish your generated static content in User Page as git submodule.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>